DC Showcase: Sgt. Rock is a action, war, animation film directed by Bruce Timm.
Just after recovering from losing his entire unit in battle, Sgt.
Rock leads a special army of commandos against a Nazi secret research base.
Sgt. Rock (voice), played by Karl Urban.
Lt. Shrieve (voice), played by Keith Ferguson.
The Iron Major (voice), played by William Salyers.
Nurse (voice), played by Audrey Wasilewski.
DC Showcase: Sgt.
Rock is an American animated short war superhero film based on the titular character, directed by Bruce Timm,
written by Louise Simonson, Walter Simonson and Tim Sheridan, and produced by Warner Bros.
Animation and DC Entertainment.
The short was included as part of the home media release of Batman: Hush.
It is the first DC Showcase installment in eight
years since DC Showcase: Catwoman.
The tone is thought_provoking.